JACOB **BOGNER**

47 Whitewood Road, Milford MA 01757 · 508-377-2302 boginator55@gmail.com

Skilled in Information Technology, Networking, Computer Science, Microsoft Excel, Management, Customer Service, and Microsoft Word. Working as a student Undergraduate Engineer, with experience in MATLAB and Java. Experienced In-House service technician with a demonstrated history of working in the fast-food restaurant industry. Highly familiar with the design, operation, safety standards, and maintenance of machines and equipment within the industry. Strong professional working toward a Computer Science degree with a minor in Mathematics from Bridgewater State University.

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2018

STUDENT UNDERGRADUATE ENGINNER, THE CHARLES STARK DRAPER LABORATORY

- Experience configuring and testing mission-critical/fault-tolerant systems
 - Virtualization
- Hardware and software development and testing for Project Lifecycle Management Systems
 - Assisted in the creation of a database and associated management system to store, classify, and run various permutations of test cases
 - Assisted in the automation of software testing for the platform

2015 - PRESENT

OPERATIONS TECHNOLOGY, SELLIA GROUP LLC MCDONALD'S

- Certified swing manager (2017-present)
- Operations Technology (2016-present)
- Duties include the general upkeep and maintenance of restaurant infrastructure and technology across several locations. Specialties include:
 - Certified to work on Taylor commercial grills and Taylor heat-treatment shake/soft serve freezers. Well-versed in the electrical, mechanical, and refrigeration systems involved in installing, maintaining, and repairing these units
 - Troubleshooting, maintenance, and routine upgrades to POS systems, KVS systems, and restaurant servers
 - Coordinating equipment troubleshooting, upgrades, and repairs with an extensive supplier network
 - Troubleshooting, maintenance, in-depth repair, and general upkeep of Taylor, Manitowoc, Henny Penny, Prince Castle, Bunn, etc. commercial foodservice equipment

EDUCATION

2012-2016

DIPLOMA, MARIAN HIGH SCHOOL (FRAMINGHAM, MA)

2016- PRESENT

BRIDGEWATER STATE UNIVERSITY

Working towards a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science with a Minor in Mathematics

SKILLS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- 10 years of experience studying piano
- 50-Mile Canoe Trip (Troop 4 High Adventure-Allagash, ME)
- 50-Mile Backpacking Trip (Troop 4 High Adventure-Camp Tahosa, CO)
- 50-Mile Canoe Trip (Troop 4 High Adventure-NY)
- Familiar with the design and operation of Fire-Lite/Honeywell branded Fire Alarm and Life Safety Systems
- Proficient in C++, Java, Python, and MATLAB
- Experienced with Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint

- Experienced with the electrical, mechanical, and refrigeration design, operation, and maintenance of Taylor commercial grade grills and heat treatment soft-serve/shake freezers
- Certified for Electrical Safe Work Practices in the commercial foodservice industry (AVO Training Institute, Jan 2019)
- Certified Taylor Service Technician (Taylor Technical Center, July 2019)
- Eagle Scout with Troop 4 Milford MA (Awarded May 2016)
- National Honor Society (2013-2015)
- International Thespian society (2014-Present)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

- St. Mary's Parish (Milford, MA) volunteer
 - Provided technical (computer software) assistance to choir director and organist with preparation of concert programs
 - Food With Friends volunteer
 - Altar Server
- Pine St. Inn Homeless Shelter (Boston, MA) volunteer
 - o 1st Monday of every moth
 - Serve dinner at homeless shelter
- Benjamin Franklin Classical Charter Public School Capstone Project
 - Designed and built handicap barrier according to specifications set out by Milford Board of Health
 - o Installed handicap barrier on Upper Charles River Bike Trail